{
  "questions": [
    {
      "type": "text",
      "question": "1. What is the capital of Tamil nadu?",
      "answer": "Chennai"
    },
    {
      "type": "radio",
      "question": "2.Which is the largest planet in our solar system?",
      "options": ["Earth", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
      "answer": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
      "type": "checkbox",
      "question": "3. Select all prime numbers:",
      "options": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
      "answer": ["2", "3", "5"]
    },
    {
      "type": "dropdown",
      "question": "4. What is the capital of Japan?",
      "options": ["Tokyo", "Kyoto", "Osaka", "Nagoya"],
      "answer": "Tokyo"
    },
    {
      "type": "radio",
      "question": "5.How many days in a week?",
      "options": ["5", "4", "7", "6"],
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "type": "text",
      "question": "6.How many months in a year?",
      "options": ["23", "10", "11", "12"],
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "type": "dropdown",
      "question": "7.What is the largest lake in the world??",
      "options": ["Caspian Sea", "Baikal", "Lake Superior", "Ontario"],
      "answer": "Baikal"
    },
    {
      "type": "radio",
      "question": "8.What is the official currency of Japan??",
      "options": ["Won", "Yen", "Yuan", "Dollars"],
      "answer": "Yen"
    },
    {
      "type": "radio",
      "question": "9. Who is the captain of Indian Cricket team?",
      "options": ["Dhoni", "Rohit sharma", "Virat kohli", "Dravid"],
      "answer": "Yen"
    },
    {
      "type": "radio",
      "question": "10. Who is the Director of Indian 2 ?",
      "options": ["Shankar", "Atlee", "Raja mouli", "karthick subburaj"],
      "answer": "Yen"
    }
  ]
}
